[
  {
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a41",
    "correctAnswer": "Ghana",
    "options": ["India", "Australia", "Egypt", "Ghana"],
    "question": "The Gold Coast gained its independence from Great Britain in 1957 and formed part of which new country?"
  },
  {
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f947",
    "category": "film_and_tv",
    "correctAnswer": "Pirates of the Caribbean",
    "options": [
      "The Godfather",
      "Pirates of the Caribbean",
      "The Silence of the Lambs",
      "The Birds"
    ],
    "question": "Which film contains the character 'Captain Jack Sparrow'?"
  },
  {
    "category": "science",
    "id": "6461407d4d46e537ca8cd9d7",
    "correctAnswer": "Magnetron",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Resistor", "Magnetron", "Diode", "Transistor"],
    "question": "What kind of electronic tube is used to produce microwaves?"
  },
  {
    "category": "arts_and_literature",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95135a",
    "correctAnswer": "Baroque",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Classical", "Renaissance", "Baroque", "Gothic"],
    "question": "Which 17th and early 18th century movement in painting is characterized by great drama, deep colour, intense light and dark shadows?"
  },
  {
    "category": "history",
    "id": "62611fc34b176d54800e3d6f",
    "correctAnswer": "1971",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["1971", "1957", "1964", "1978"],
    "question": "When was the first email sent?"
  },
  {
    "category": "society_and_culture",
    "id": "6293ebc77f41d6338b96eebf",
    "correctAnswer": "Christopher Columbus",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Napoleon Bonaparte",
      "Martin Luther",
      "Marco Polo",
      "Christopher Columbus"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these people was an Italian explorer who landed in America?"
  },
  {
    "category": "geography",
    "id": "6237403bcb85f7ce9e949ce9",
    "correctAnswer": "Dominica",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Romania",
      "Sierra Leone",
      "Antigua and Barbuda",
      "Dominica"
    ],
    "question": "Roseau is the capital city of which country?"
  },
  {
    "category": "arts_and_literature",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f95b",
    "correctAnswer": "Post Office",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tinker",
      "My Life As a Man",
      "Post Office",
      "Nine Stories"
    ],
    "question": "Which book contains the character 'Henry Chinaski'?"
  },
  {
    "category": "arts_and_literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e7e",
    "correctAnswer": "Voltaire",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Voltaire",
      "Stendhal",
      "Paulo Coelho",
      "Isabel Allende"
    ],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Candide'?"
  },
  {
    "category": "music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c7e",
    "correctAnswer": "U2",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Public Image Ltd.", "U2", "The Script", "The Cure"],
    "question": "Which Irish rock band released the studio album 'All That You Can't Leave Behind'?"
  }
]
